const arr = [{"id":0,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following is not a part of fluorescence in situ hybridization (FISH)?","answers":[{"option":"Amplification of DNA","bool":true},{"option":"Identification chromosomal aberrations","bool":false},{"option":"Detection gene deletions","bool":false},{"option":"Identification gene mutations","bool":false},{"option":"Mapping of genes","bool":false}]},{"id":1,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following diseases requires genetic counseling?","answers":[{"option":"Angelman syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Hereditary porphyrias","bool":false},{"option":"Down syndrome","bool":true},{"option":"Prader-Willi syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Essential galactosemia","bool":false}]},{"id":2,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"A person is unable to walk. What is this called?","answers":[{"option":"Impairment","bool":false},{"option":"Handicap","bool":false},{"option":"Abnormality","bool":false},{"option":"Disability","bool":true},{"option":"Retardation","bool":false}]},{"id":3,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"People doing regular weight training are low risk for which condition?","answers":[{"option":"Osteoporosis","bool":true},{"option":"Diabetes mellitus","bool":false},{"option":"Anxiety","bool":false},{"option":"Coronary artery disease","bool":false},{"option":"Eating disorder","bool":false}]},{"id":4,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following describes pemphigus vulgaris histology?","answers":[{"option":"Subbasilar acontholytic","bool":false},{"option":"Suprabasilar acantholytic","bool":true},{"option":"Suprabasilar nonacantholytic","bool":false},{"option":"Subepithelial acantholytic","bool":false},{"option":"Subdermal nonacontholytic","bool":false}]},{"id":5,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What histopathology does bullous pemphigoid have?","answers":[{"option":"Subbasilar acantholytic","bool":false},{"option":"Subepidermal nonacantholytic","bool":true},{"option":"Supraepidermal acantholytic","bool":false},{"option":"Subepidermal acantholytic","bool":false},{"option":"Suprabasilar acantholytic","bool":false}]},{"id":6,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Alkaptonuria has which of the following characteristic symptoms?","answers":[{"option":"Failure to thrive","bool":false},{"option":"Fruity breath","bool":false},{"option":"Dark urine","bool":true},{"option":"Skin discoloration","bool":false},{"option":"Speech retardation","bool":false}]},{"id":7,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"A 6-year-old child presents with itchy scalp lesions and hair loss. There is a patchy inflamed area on their scalp and a lack of hair growth over it. Parents give a history of 1-week camping trip. What is the diagnosis?","answers":[{"option":"Tinea corporus","bool":false},{"option":"Tinea capitis","bool":true},{"option":"Seborrheic keratosis","bool":false},{"option":"Alopecia","bool":false},{"option":"Seborrheic dermatitis","bool":false}]},{"id":8,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"A raised alpha-fetoprotein level raises the suspicion for what congenital birth defect in a fetus?","answers":[{"option":"Congenital cataract","bool":false},{"option":"Patau's syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Edward's syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Meningocele","bool":true},{"option":"Congenital deafness","bool":false}]},{"id":9,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Study of changes in gene frequencies in population of organisms along with the evolutionary and adaptation effects is called what?","answers":[{"option":"Bioinformatics","bool":false},{"option":"Ecology","bool":false},{"option":"Population genetics","bool":true},{"option":"Genomics","bool":false},{"option":"Genetic linkage","bool":false}]},{"id":10,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"The Hardy-Weinberg equilibrium for genotypic frequencies is best defined by which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"p + q = 1","bool":false},{"option":"q^2","bool":false},{"option":"p^2","bool":false},{"option":"2pq","bool":false},{"option":"p^2 + 2pq + q^2 = 1","bool":true}]},{"id":11,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"A 4-year-old boy presents to the clinic with cough, fever, and malaise for the past 2 weeks. Upon general inspection, the child has epicanthic folds, depressed nasal bridge, broad forehead, small ears, and a single palmar crease on his right hand. What is your first diagnosis on this child?","answers":[{"option":"Prader-Willi syndrome","bool":false},{"option":"Down's syndrome","bool":true},{"option":"Cystic fibrosis","bool":false},{"option":"Autism","bool":false},{"option":"Angelaman syndrome","bool":false}]},{"id":12,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Pencil grip and magnifying glass are what sort of tools?","answers":[{"option":"Low tech","bool":true},{"option":"Analogue","bool":false},{"option":"Very high tech","bool":false},{"option":"High tech","bool":false},{"option":"Mid tech","bool":false}]},{"id":13,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"An augmentative communication device is what kind of tool?","answers":[{"option":"Very high tech","bool":false},{"option":"Very low tech","bool":false},{"option":"Mid tech","bool":false},{"option":"High tech","bool":true},{"option":"Low tech","bool":false}]},{"id":14,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"The dynamo chat box is used for which of the following situations?","answers":[{"option":"People who cannot hear properly","bool":false},{"option":"People who are not accustomed to social environments","bool":false},{"option":"People with communication problems","bool":false},{"option":"People who cannot speak","bool":true},{"option":"People who cannot comprehend their surroundings","bool":false}]},{"id":15,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Lying prone 3 times a day for 15 minutes prevents which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Hip flexion contractures","bool":true},{"option":"Hip extension contractures","bool":false},{"option":"Dorsiflexion contractures","bool":false},{"option":"Leg flexion contractures","bool":false},{"option":"Plantar flexion contractures","bool":false}]},{"id":16,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Fractures of the distal tibia are treated with which of the following orthosis?","answers":[{"option":"Knee orthosis with a patellar-tendon brace","bool":true},{"option":"Thigh orthosis connected to leg","bool":false},{"option":"Hip-ankle orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Foot orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Knee-hip orthosis","bool":false}]},{"id":17,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which orthosis is used in osteoarthritis?","answers":[{"option":"Functional knee orthosis","bool":true},{"option":"Prophylactic knee orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Rehabilitative knee orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Preoperative knee orthosis","bool":false},{"option":"Structural knee orthosis","bool":false}]},{"id":18,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What prosthesis uses power from the muscles in a stump?","answers":[{"option":"Electromagnetic prosthesis","bool":false},{"option":"Mechanical prosthesis","bool":false},{"option":"Externally powered prosthesis","bool":false},{"option":"Myoelectric prosthesis","bool":true},{"option":"Body powered prosthesis","bool":false}]},{"id":19,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the first and most important aspect of rehabilitation counseling?","answers":[{"option":"Trust","bool":true},{"option":"Establishing rapport","bool":false},{"option":"Exploration","bool":false},{"option":"Termination","bool":false},{"option":"Resolution","bool":false}]},{"id":20,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Eczema herpeticum is a complication of which of the following?","answers":[{"option":"Tinea","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes simplex virus","bool":true},{"option":"Poxvirus","bool":false},{"option":"Herpes zoster virus","bool":false},{"option":"Varicella zoster virus","bool":false}]},{"id":21,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the benefit of exercise in CAD?","answers":[{"option":"Increased insulin and improved glucose tolerance","bool":false},{"option":"Increased HDL and decreased triglycerides","bool":true},{"option":"Decreased HDL and increased triglycerides","bool":false},{"option":"Increased LDL and decreased total cholesterol","bool":false},{"option":"Increased total body fat","bool":false}]},{"id":22,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the most likely error that leads to chromosomal abnormalities in Down's syndrome?","answers":[{"option":"Mitotic errors","bool":false},{"option":"Genetic imprinting","bool":false},{"option":"Meiotic non-disjunction","bool":true},{"option":"Uniparental disomy","bool":false},{"option":"Robertsonian translocation","bool":false}]},{"id":23,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the best treatment for rhinophyma?","answers":[{"option":"Topical antibiotics","bool":false},{"option":"Cryotherapy","bool":false},{"option":"Dermabrasion","bool":true},{"option":"Topical steroids","bool":false},{"option":"Topical immunosuppressants","bool":false}]},{"id":24,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following are antigen-presenting cells?","answers":[{"option":"Langerhan's cells","bool":true},{"option":"Kupffer cells","bool":false},{"option":"Neutrophils","bool":false},{"option":"Killer T cells","bool":false},{"option":"Koilocytes","bool":false}]},{"id":25,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following cells is responsible for sensations of stretching of skin?","answers":[{"option":"Ruffini's cells","bool":true},{"option":"Pacinian corpuscle","bool":false},{"option":"Merkel's cells","bool":false},{"option":"Melanocytes","bool":false},{"option":"Meissner's corpuscles","bool":false}]},{"id":26,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"The Malpighian layer in the skin is comprised of which layers?","answers":[{"option":"Stratum corneum and lucidum","bool":false},{"option":"Stratum granulosum and lucidum","bool":false},{"option":"Stratum basale and hypodermis","bool":false},{"option":"Stratum basale and spinosum","bool":true},{"option":"Stratum spinosum and granulosum","bool":false}]},{"id":27,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following has the germinative zone of the nail?","answers":[{"option":"Hypodermis","bool":false},{"option":"Nail root","bool":false},{"option":"Matrix","bool":true},{"option":"Epidermis","bool":false},{"option":"Nail bed","bool":false}]},{"id":28,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Fascicular growth is seen in which of the following conditions?","answers":[{"option":"Halo nevus","bool":false},{"option":"Dysplastic nevus","bool":false},{"option":"Meyerson nevus","bool":false},{"option":"Congenital nevus","bool":false},{"option":"Spitz nevus","bool":true}]},{"id":29,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following symptoms is not seen in longstanding scabies?","answers":[{"option":"Rhinitis","bool":true},{"option":"Itching","bool":false},{"option":"Crusting","bool":false},{"option":"Blistering","bool":false},{"option":"Sores","bool":false}]},{"id":30,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the most common symptom of scabies?","answers":[{"option":"Rhinitis","bool":false},{"option":"Burning","bool":false},{"option":"Itching","bool":true},{"option":"Blistering","bool":false},{"option":"Crusting","bool":false}]},{"id":31,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What are the nail changes seen in psoriasis?","answers":[{"option":"Koilonychia","bool":false},{"option":"Pitting","bool":true},{"option":"Dystrophy","bool":false},{"option":"Onychomycosis","bool":false},{"option":"Pterygium","bool":false}]},{"id":32,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the surgical procedure for nose damage of the tip and ala?","answers":[{"option":"Gunderson flaps","bool":false},{"option":"Transposition flap","bool":false},{"option":"Rotation flap","bool":false},{"option":"Bilobed flap","bool":true},{"option":"Tarsorrhaphy","bool":false}]},{"id":33,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which drug is given for tinea capitis?","answers":[{"option":"Griseofulvin","bool":false},{"option":"Praziquantel","bool":false},{"option":"Terbinafine","bool":true},{"option":"Amphotericin B","bool":false},{"option":"Albendazole","bool":false}]},{"id":34,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which skin lesion is not associated with sun exposure?","answers":[{"option":"Acute intermittent porphyria","bool":true},{"option":"Squamous cell carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Melanoma","bool":false},{"option":"Basal cell carcinoma","bool":false},{"option":"Actinic keratosis","bool":false}]},{"id":35,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is a characteristic lesion of subacute eczema?","answers":[{"option":"Glistening scales and crusts","bool":true},{"option":"Vesicles","bool":false},{"option":"Pruritic papules","bool":false},{"option":"Lichenification","bool":false},{"option":"Fissuring","bool":false}]},{"id":36,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following is a non-invasive dermatological treatment for the face?","answers":[{"option":"Bilobed flap procedure","bool":false},{"option":"Laser","bool":true},{"option":"Cryosurgery","bool":false},{"option":"Conservative excision","bool":false},{"option":"Dermabrasion","bool":false}]},{"id":37,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following describes a person responsible for ensuring the patient is managing their stress and psychologically functioning well during rehabilitation?","answers":[{"option":"Vocational therapist","bool":false},{"option":"Physiotherapist","bool":false},{"option":"Physiatrist","bool":false},{"option":"Neuropsychologist","bool":true},{"option":"Occupational therapist","bool":false}]},{"id":38,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the most common exercise for strengthening stump muscles after a lower limb amputation?","answers":[{"option":"Hip extension","bool":true},{"option":"Adduction","bool":false},{"option":"Dorsiflexion","bool":false},{"option":"Hip flexion","bool":false},{"option":"Knee flexion","bool":false}]},{"id":39,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is the most common exercise for strengthening stump muscles after an upper limb amputation?","answers":[{"option":"Pronation","bool":false},{"option":"Elbow extension","bool":true},{"option":"Back flexion","bool":false},{"option":"Elbow flexion","bool":false},{"option":"Palmar flexion","bool":false}]},{"id":40,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"A recessive disorder is phenotypically expressed as dominant. Which of the following best describes this phenomenon?","answers":[{"option":"Codominant","bool":false},{"option":"Incomplete penetrance","bool":false},{"option":"Mosaicism","bool":false},{"option":"Pleiotropy","bool":false},{"option":"Pseudodominant","bool":true}]},{"id":41,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Which of the following is best described as 'health status or functioning of a particular part of a body is disturbed'?","answers":[{"option":"Disability","bool":false},{"option":"Dysfunction","bool":false},{"option":"Degradation","bool":false},{"option":"Impairment","bool":true},{"option":"Handicap","bool":false}]},{"id":42,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"What is polyploidy?","answers":[{"option":"Only 3 paired sets of chromosomes","bool":false},{"option":"> 2 paired sets of chromosomes","bool":true},{"option":"A multiple of 23 number of chromosomes","bool":false},{"option":"< 2 paired sets of chromosomes","bool":false},{"option":"Chromosomes with unpaired and paired sets","bool":false}]},{"id":43,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"Psychological management as well as pharmacological therapy is carried out by which of the following professionals?","answers":[{"option":"Physiotherapist","bool":false},{"option":"Psychiatrist","bool":true},{"option":"Pharmacist","bool":false},{"option":"Physiatrist","bool":false},{"option":"Therapist","bool":false}]},{"id":44,"info":"4th-year/drg/2018","question":"If a person catches fire what is the immediate movement they must make to ensure minimum damage to themselves?","answers":[{"option":"Hold still","bool":false},{"option":"Jump in a pool","bool":false},{"option":"Call for help by reaching a phone","bool":false},{"option":"Stop, drop, and roll","bool":true},{"option":"Jump and flee","bool":false}]}]
export default arr